<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="item_titles">
        <item>Suriyani</item>
        <item>Rechado</item>
        <item>Kovalam</item>
        <item>Tikka Twist</item>
        <item>Peri Peri</item>
        <item>Kasuri Methi</item>
        <item>Nizam-e-Khas</item>
        <item>Creamy Ajwain</item>
        <item>Peppy BBQ</item>
        <item>Aai\'s Masala</item>
        <item>Jaffna</item>
        <item>Madras Magic</item>
        <item>Kolkata Calling</item>
        <item>Comint</item>
        <item>Fresh Thai</item>
        <item>Chilli Cheese</item>


    </string-array>

    <string-array name="item_subtitles">
        <item>GOD\'S OWN SPICE MIX</item>
        <item>GOAN SIZZLE</item>
        <item>KERALITE BEACH DELIGHT</item>
        <item>PUNJAB DA PUNCH!</item>
        <item>PORTUGUESE FIRE</item>
        <item>A CLASSIC COMBO</item>
        <item>MEMORIES FROM HYD’BAD</item>
        <item>PROUDLY NORTH INDIAN</item>
        <item>DARK AND DELICIOUS</item>
        <item>COASTAL MAHARASHTRA</item>
        <item>A SRI LANKAN SENSATION</item>
        <item>CHENNAI SUPERSTAR</item>
        <item>TASTE OF BENGAL</item>
        <item>BURST OF FRESHNESS</item>
        <item>AROMAS OF THAILAND</item>
        <item>CREAMY TIDBITS</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="item_descriptions">
        <item>This one comes from Kerala\'s Syrian Christian aka Suriyani Kitchen. Fresh spices, including coriander, pepper and green cardamom, create a delicious whirl of taste.</item>
        <item>This spicy-tangy Goan staple uses Kashmiri chillies, garlic, cumin and peppercorns, with tamarind playing a vital role in bringing out its robust and lively flavour.</item>
        <item>Fresh curry leaves join hands with slivers of dried red chilly to create this refreshingly aromatic spicy dish rooted in coastal Kerala.</item>
        <item>A spin on the iconic medium-spicy marinade concocted out of a blend of North Indian spices smoothened by fresh yogurt.</item>
        <item>This fiery Portuguese sauce brings together pungent bird\'s eye chilles and garlic, pepper, white wine vinegar and olive oil to leave a sizzle you will love instantly.</item>
        <item>The richness of freshly ground spices comes together with the pungent spike of green chilly and slightly bitter bite of dried fenugreek.</item>
        <item>Inspired by Hyderabad’s iconic biryani, this marinade blends freshly ground garam masala, ginger, garlic and green chilly, tempered with fresh coriander, curd and lemon juice.</item>
        <item>Ajwain, with its thyme-like aroma, is the king of this mix, ably complemented by the indulgent flavours of cream and yoghurt.</item>
        <item>The classic chill-out companion in the form of a smoky in-house sauce. Remember the outdoors and the grills.</item>
        <item>From Alibag’s coastal cuisine, comes this unique, flavourful and rich spice mixture blending more elements too numerous to be mentioned here!</item>
        <item>Unique to Jaffna’s Sri Lankan Tamil cuisine for both seafood and meat curries, this spice mix involves blending individually dryroasted ingredients, to create a masala that is replete with flavour.</item>
        <item>Aromatic and flavourful spices come together to create the quintessential Chettinad blend that leaves a delicious, lingering taste in your mouth...</item>
        <item>This mild tempered marinade melding the pungency of mustard, spikes of green chillies and a hint of cumin reminds you of Kolkata in every bite.</item>
        <item>Fragrant herbs, almost straight from the farm, go into flavouring this mild marinade, with a bit of chilly and ginger for that added punch.</item>
        <item>Intensely aromatic lemon grass and the oh-so-spicy bird’s eye chilly get together with galangal and kaffir lime in this fresh, fragrant and fabulous offering.</item>
        <item>Melt-in-your-mouth morsels concocted out of cream and cheese, uplifted with a hint of chilly and fresh coriander. A refreshing taste of chicken.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="item_prices">
        <item>140.00</item>
        <item>140.00</item>
        <item>140.00</item>
        <item>140.00</item>
        <item>140.00</item>
        <item>140.00</item>
        <item>140.00</item>
        <item>150.00</item>
        <item>150.00</item>
        <item>140.00</item>
        <item>140.00</item>
        <item>140.00</item>
        <item>140.00</item>
        <item>140.00</item>
        <item>140.00</item>
        <item>150.00</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="item_flavours1">
        <item>Spicy</item>
        <item>Spicy</item>
        <item>Mild</item>
        <item>Mild</item>
        <item>Spicy</item>
        <item>Mild</item>
        <item>Mild</item>
        <item>Mild</item>
        <item>Mild</item>
        <item>Spicy</item>
        <item>Mild</item>
        <item>Mild</item>
        <item>Mild</item>
        <item>Fresh Herbs</item>
        <item>Spicy</item>
        <item>Fresh Herbs</item>


    </string-array>

    <string-array name="item_flavours2">
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item>Fresh Herbs</item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item>Microwave</item>
        <item>Fresh Herbs</item>
        <item>Microwave</item>


    </string-array>


    <string-array name="promo_code">
        <item>FF22</item>
        <item>C1B1</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="promo_desc">
        <item>Get flat 10% off on total cart</item>
        <item>Get 20% off on total cart if number of items is greater than 5</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>